here are the stories were covering this
ここにはこれをカバーしていた物語があります
week in the category 5 TV newsroom a
カテゴリー 5の 週に TVニュースルーム a
newfound exploit in Windows and DFS
Windowsと DFS での新しい発見
implementation will crash the machines
実装によってマシンがクラッシュする
by simply including a short string
短い文字列 を含めるだけで
within an image on a website a French
ウェブサイトの画像内で フランス語
school is using facial recognition to
学校は顔認識を使用しています
find out whether students find out when
いつ生徒がいつ出会うか調べる
students aren't paying attention a new
学生は新しい注意を払っていません
found malware on Android devices could
Android搭載 端末の マルウェアが見つかりました
be on your phone and Intel has already
お使いの携帯電話 に 搭載されていて 、 インテルはすでに
surpassed AMD's thread Ripper these
AMDのスレッドリッパーを上回った
stories are coming right up don't go
物語はすぐに来ていない
anywhere
どこでも
Jeff Weston Yellin you're building a
あなたが構築している ジェフ・ウェストン イェリン
brand-new beautiful website
真新しい新しい ウェブサイト
what are you alright
あなたは大丈夫ですか？
you're a terrible actor what does where
あなたはひどい俳優ですどこで何をしますか
acting comes into play I don't know
演技は私にはわからない
where Isaac you're supposed to act
イサクはあなたが行動すべき場所です
ok fair enough I'm building a really
[OK]を公正に十分な、私は 本当にを 構築 し ています
cool website are you building a really
クールなウェブサイトはあなたが 本当に
cool website you need hosting one of the
あなたの いずれかをホストしている必要がありますクールなウェブサイト
things about a hosting account is you
ホスティングアカウントに関することはあなたです
don't want to have limitations put on
制限をかけたくない
your website it's sure how much hard
あなたのウェブサイトはどれくらい難しいか確信しています
drive space you have how many email
あなたがいくつの電子メールを持っているドライブスペース
accounts how many domains can point to
いくつのドメインがポイントできるのかを説明します
it well we've got an amazing deal for
それはうまくいっています
you
君は
for a very limited time cap 5 dot TV
非常に限られた時間キャップのために 5ドットテレビ
slash dream host for just $5 and a bit
ちょうど 5ドルと少しの ために夢のホストを スラッシュ
of change per month you are going to get
あなたが得るつもりの月あたりの変化の
unlimited web site hosting unlimited
無制限のWebサイト ホスティング無制限
email accounts on that hosting service
そのホスティングサービスの電子メールアカウント
you are also going to receive a free
あなたはまた、無料で
domain name the roof of your own calm
ドメイン名 あなた自身の落ち着きの屋根
dice to put that amazing website that
その驚くほどのウェブサイトを置くためにサイコロ
you've been working on on there if you
あなたが そこに取り組んで きたのは 、あなたが
run if you want to build a WordPress
あなた が WordPress を 構築し たい場合に実行 し ます。
site fine
サイトの細かい
sign up cap five dot TV slash green hose
サインキャップ5ドットTVスラッシュグリーンホース
still put a little papers on it just
それでも ちょっと紙を 貼って
don't do it but hey it's a great deal
それをしないでくださいねえ、それは大したことだ
folks best deal you're going to find
あなたが見つけようとしている人には最高の
five dollars and change per month go to
5ドルと1 ヶ月あたりの変更は
cap five dot TV / dream host I'm Sasha
私は サーシャ だ 5ドットTV /夢のホストをキャップ
dramatis and here are the top stories
ドラマチスとはここにトップの物語です
for the week of May 31st 2017
2017年5月31日の週
it's been a bad month for Windows 7
それはWindows 7のための悪い月だった
users the widespread wanna cry
ユーザーは広範囲に 泣き たい
ransomware hit a ton of Windows 7
ransomwareはWindows 7のトンを打つ
machines and now a new bug has been
新しいバグがありました
discovered that will slow down and crash
減速してクラッシュすることが発見された
Windows 7 and Windows 8 the bug allows a
Windows 7および Windows 8 では、このバグにより
malicious website to try and load an
悪意のあるWebサイトに
image file with the dollar side an MF
ドルサイド MF の画像ファイル
key name in the directory path windows
ディレクトリパスウィンドウのキー名
uses a dollar sign MFT for special
特別に ドル記号 MFTを 使用する
metadata files that are used by NTFS
NTFSで使用されるメタデータファイル
file system and Windows 7 and Windows 8
ファイルシステムとWindows 7 とWindows 8
fail to handle this directory name
このディレクトリ名を処理できません
correctly the bug has been tested on
正しくバグがテストされました
Windows 7 PC with the default Internet
既定のインターネットを搭載した Windows 7 PC
Explorer browser using the file name C
ファイル 名C を使用するエクスプローラブラウザ
colon slash dollar sign MFT / 1 2 3 in a
コロンスラッシュドル記号MFT / 1 2 3 in a
website image the test cause the machine
ウェブサイトの画像 テストの原因マシン
to slow down to the point where you have
あなたが持っている ポイントまで減速する
to reboot in order to get it working
それを動作させるためにリブートする
again some machines may even blue screen
再びいくつかのマシンはブルースクリーン
eventually as the file system looks to
最終的にファイルシステムが見えるようになります
that file and all other apps are unable
そのファイルと他のすべてのアプリはできません
to access files the strange bug doesn't
ファイルにアクセスするには奇妙なバグはありません
affect Windows 10 users and it's similar
Windows 10 ユーザーにも似ています
to an old problem in Windows 95 and
Windowsの95 の古い問題へと
windows 98 where references to C : flash
C： flash への参照がある Windows 98
con flash con would crash a machine the
マシンをクラッシュさせて
NTFS bug appears to have been discovered
NTFSのバグが発見されたようです
early last week and have been reported
先週 早く 、報告されている
to Microsoft it's not clear when
マイクロソフト には、いつそれが明確でないのか
Microsoft will deliver a fix for the
マイクロソフトは、
problem but it affects Windows Vista
問題がWindows Vistaに影響する
which is unsupported Windows 7 and
Windows 7と 、サポートされていない とします
Windows 8 machines Wow that's do we want
Windows 8のマシンうわー 、それは私たちが望むものです
to like see how easy it is for someone
好きには誰かのためにそれがいかに簡単か見る
to compromise this in like 2 seconds
2秒で これ を妥協する
flat I'll just show you what we're
フラット私はちょうど私たちが何をしているかを示す
talking about here so I'm going to go to
ここで話をして、私は 行くつもり です
our website category 5 dot TV all right
私たちのウェブサイトカテゴリ5 ドットのテレビが大丈夫
so on our website you see let's say our
そう当社のウェブサイト上であなたは 私たちのを言わせて見ます
logo up at the top here right so if I
右上のロゴが上に表示されます
inspect that you can see that that is
あなたはそれがあることを見ることができる検査
image class default logo and then
画像クラスのデフォルトのロゴ、その後、
there's this file HTTP : CDN Zechariah
このファイルがありますHTTP ：CDN Zechariah
comm / image / p7 blah blah that's our
comm / image / p7 blah blah です
actual logo so what they're saying is is
実際のロゴなので、彼らが 言っていることは
by simply replacing the
単純に置き換えることにより、
that string that is our logo URL with
その文字列は私たちのロゴURLです
this simple sequel and slash dollar sign
このシンプルな続編とスラッシュドル記号
MFT slash whatever it will actually
MFT は実際に何を スラッシュ にする
bring this system to a halt unbelievable
この システムを信じられないほど停止させる
that is just being discovered now yeah
それ はちょうど今 ええ 発見されている
but then again who would think to do
しかし、誰がやり直すか
that who would think to do it but now
誰がそれをすると思うだろう が今は
that it's known and not patched right
それは知られており、 正しく パッチを当てていない こと
so many it's just to say anyone can put
とても多くの人 が 誰でも
that onto a website it's just an image
それはウェブサイト上では単なるイメージです
tag so Sasha was asking okay well do I
タグは Sashaが大丈夫です
need to click on it do I need to do any
それをクリックする必要があります私は何かをする必要があります
jig in order to have that exploit happen
その搾取を起こさせるための 治具
remember that class yeah and no the
ええ、そのクラスを覚えて いません
answer is no it's just like when you go
答えはいいえあなたが 行く ときと同じです
to our website there's our logo it shows
私たちのウェブサイトには、それが示すロゴがあります
up you didn't have to click on it to
あなたはそれをクリックする必要はありませんでした
have it all of a sudden load on the
それにすべての突然の負荷を
screen now I guess the initial question
今私は最初の質問を推測する画面
that most people would think of is why
ほとんどの人が考える 理由は
would you make your website something
あなたは何かあなたのウェブサイトを作りますか？
that crashes people's computers because
人々のコンピュータがクラッシュするのは、
you're malicious right specifically
あなたは特に悪意のある
because you're malicious why do websites
なぜあなたは悪意のあるため、ウェブサイト
distribute malware well exactly but what
マルウェアを正確に配布しますが、
I'm wondering is could somebody
私は誰かができるのだろうかと思っている
theoretically take this and say you know
理論的にこれを取って、あなたが知っていると言う
what I'm going to put this code in my
私はこのコードを私の
image so that nobody can steal my image
画像誰も私のイメージを盗むことができないように
and if they do it crashes they're not
彼らがクラッシュした場合、彼らはクラッシュ しません
it's not an it's not part of the image
それはイメージの一部ではない
it's in the image tag that tells it
それを伝えるイメージタグの中にあります
where the location of the image file is
ここで、 画像ファイルの場所は
I get that but you couldn't throw that
私はそれを得るが、あなたはそれを投げることができなかった
like because I know a lot of times you
私が何度もあなたを知っているからのように
get websites will link to other images
ウェブサイトを他の画像にリンクさせる
could you put that in there you know is
そこに置くことが できますか？
that I guess you'd crash from your site
私はあなたのサイトからクラッシュするだろうと思う
to know you oh yeah you it would crash
あなた を知っ ている ああええ、それはクラッシュするだろう
your site you could someone could hide
誰かが隠れる可能性のあるあなたのサイト
it through JavaScript right someone
誰かがJavaScriptを使用して
could make it so that a legitimate image
合法的な イメージ
becomes this string if the user has a
この文字列 は、ユーザーが
certain criteria they could have it
彼らはそれを持つことができる特定の基準
detect if the user is using Windows 7
ユーザーがWindows 7を使用しているかどうかを検出する
and they are located in Barrie Ontario
彼らはオンタリオ州バリーにあります
through geolocation change the logo to
ジオロケーションを介してロゴを
this string and therefore crash their
この文字列は、したがって、クラッシュ
computer right so they could do that
彼らはそれを行うことができるようにコンピュータ権利
yeah through JavaScript that would be
JavaScript を 使って
easy enough well mm-hmm it is crazy do
簡単にうまくいくmm-hmmそれは夢中 です
you have better news for us I do well
あなたは私がうまくいくより良いニュースがあります
depends on if you're a student
あなたが 学生 である かどうか によって決まり ます
Business School in Paris will soon begin
パリのビジネススクールはすぐに始まります
using artificial intelligence and facial
人工 知能と顔 を使って
analysis to determine whether students
学生が学生かどうかを判断する分析
are paying attention in class the
クラスで 注意 を 払って いる
software called Nestor will be used in
Nestorと呼ばれるソフトウェアは、
two online classes at the ESG Business
ESGビジネスでの 2つのオンラインクラス
School beginning in September LLC a
9月 LLC A で始まる 学校
learning the company that created Nestor
Nestorを作成した会社を学ぶ
presented the technology at an event at
での イベントで 技術を発表
the United Nations in New York two weeks
ニューヨークの 国連は 2週間
ago the idea according to LCA founder
LCA創設者の考え方
Marcel Fawcett is to use the data that
Marcel Fawcettは次のデータを使用します。
Nestor collects to improve the
ネストルは、
performance of both students and
両方の 学生 のパフォーマンスと
professors this the software uses the
このソフトウェアが使用する教授
students webcams
学生ウェブカメラ
to analyze eye movements and facial
目の動きや顔を分析する
expressions and determine whether
式を使用して
students are paying attention to a video
学生は ビデオ に 注意 を 払っ ている
lecture it then formulates quizzes based
講義でそれに基づいてクイズを作成する
on the content covered during moments of
の 瞬間に カバーされたコンテンツ
inattentiveness
不注意
professors would also be able to
教授はまた、
identify moments when students attention
学生の注意を喚起する瞬間を特定する
waned which could help to improve their
自分を改善するのに役立つ可能性が 衰え
teaching I was wondering where this was
教えて、 私はこれがどこだったのだろう
going and I was thinking you know what's
私はあなたが何を知っていると思っていた
to stop them from having it running in
それはで実行されていること からそれらを停止するには
the background and just be watching a
背景と ちょうど見ている
YouTube video right but then and what is
YouTubeのビデオは正しいですが、それは何ですか
still to stop them because they may be
彼らがいるかもしれないので、まだそれらを停止する
attentive to that but because it quizzes
それに気配りが、それはクイズ理由
them right something you said there is
あなたがそこにいると言ったもの
interesting though it it quizzes them on
それはそれをクイズにもかかわらず興味深い
the questions that were covered during
その間にカバーされた質問
the moments of unattentive Ness yes so
はい そう unattentiveネスの瞬間
very smart super sneaky so it's the
非常にスマートな 超卑​​劣なので、それは
system the AI thinks oh they're not
AIは彼らがそうではないと思うシステム
paying attention right now generates a
今すぐ 注意を払うと、
list of questions how far how smart is
どのようにスマートであるかの質問のリスト
the AI if you get those dollars to our
あなたが 私たちに それらのドルを手に入れたらAI
glasses that look like those really big
本当に 大きい もののように 見える眼鏡
open eyes could you just nap with your
開いている目は、あなただけで昼寝できますか？
considering you can like break in the
あなたは、
two-factor authentication with a picture
画像による二要素認証
right yeah yes oh yeah wow that really
はい 、そうです
intended watching your eyes so you've
あなたの目 を 見ているように
got a but people would learn it's like
持っているが、人々はそれが似ていることを学ぶだろう
the lie detector test and people who
嘘発見器のテスト と人々
have been trained to overcome it you
それを克服するように訓練されている
couldn't you just like learn to be like
あなたは似ていることを学ぶのが好きではないでしょうか
right thinking about stuff and just it's
物事について正しい考えをし ている だけです
like what you're doing right now but the
あなたが今やっているようなものの
first question that comes to my head is
私の頭に来る最初の質問です
are these tests gradable and if so does
これらのテストは段階的であるかどうか、そうであれば
that then in turn create a legal
それから 順番に 法律を 作ります
liability where somebody I don't even
誰かが私がいなくても責任を負う
know if that's the intention no Jeff no
それが意図である かどうか を 知り ません。
maybe not but like imagine rolling this
おそらくそうではないが、 これを 想像するように
out it's a loss
それは損失だ
cool sure tomato so right we're right
冷たい確かにトマト そう、そうだよね
but they're going to test you all his
しかし、彼らはあなたのすべてをテストするつもりです
stuff the test in a unit it's not an
テストを ユニットに入れないでください
examination it is did did this lesson
審査されましたこのレッスン
sink in right like if I could go back
私が戻ってもいいかのように右に沈む
over tonight's episode and quiz you on
今夜のエピソードとあなたの上でクイズ
the things that you you know went like
あなたが知っていること が好きになった
this while it was happening or the kids
これが 起こっている間、または子供たち
ran into the room and distracted you and
部屋 に飛び込み、あなたとあなたを気晴らしました。
then I quizzed you on that it would be a
その後、私はそれが可能だろうとあなたの上の事情聴取しました
oh I need to learn that because I it
ああ、 私はそれ ので、 それを学ぶ必要があります
calls you on it but does it factor in
あなたにそれを呼びますが、
things like ninety percent of what you
あなた のものの 90％ のようなもの
hear doesn't pertain I'm sure yeah yeah
聞こえない私は確かにええええ
I just I am okay with this in the
私はちょうど私がこれで大丈夫です
classroom I would be really upset if
私が もし 本当に 動揺 だろう教室
they brought this into the workplace or
彼らはこれを職場に持ち込んだり、
into my home life was husband's
私の家庭生活に は夫のものだった
everywhere going yes here don't bring it
どこにいてもここにはいりません
into the house don't bring it in a
家に 持ち帰っ て はならない
really interesting idea though I think
私は 思うけど本当に面白いアイデア
as an educational tool yeah yeah yes
教育ツールとしてのええええ はい
it's all sorry for the purposes of
それはすべて の目的のために 申し訳ありません
improving lesson plans or making things
授業計画の改善やもの作り
more dynamic I could see that but sure
よりダイナミックな私はそれを見ることができたが、確かに
but does a factor in or like if
のような要因を
somebody's bearing their head no I don't
誰かが 私の頭を 抱えて いない
like I'm a questions guy but I like to
私は質問者ですが、私は好きです
question you need to add other questions
他の質問 を追加する必要がある 質問
hiding back to an episode that we did a
我々が行った エピソードに隠れている
couple weeks ago where we looked at the
何週間か 前に
sessions of our web viewers hey the
私たちのウェブビューアのセッション
users were on our website we actually
ユーザーは私たちのウェブサイト に 実際にいた
watched it like a video and so by doing
それはビデオのように見て、そうすることによって
that it gave us an opportunity to see oh
それは私たちに オハイオ に会う機会を与えた
that could be improved on our website so
私たちのウェブサイトでそれを 改善 することができます
could we then look back at our what our
私たちは、私たちが
show if this was in the educational
これが 教育の中で あっ た かどうかを 示す
programming that was being watched
監視されていたプログラミング
see and see oh hello Henry's fidgeting
ヘンリーのそわそわ ハロー ああ見て見ます
right now so you know this is whatever
今、あなたはこれが 何でも 知っているので
your thing is hello how heartbreaking
あなたのことはこんにちはどのように悲惨なです
would that be actually like in the part
実際にはその部分に似ていますか？
when you think about a way if you're the
もしあなたがもしあなたが
teacher say we could see it you're like
先生は、私たちは、あなたが似ている、それを見ることができたと言います
oh every time I talk they look away
ああ、 たびに私は 彼らが離れて見て 話す
every time I say something they take a
私が何かを言うたびに、 彼ら は
drink yeah you become the drinking game
飲むええ、あなたは飲みゲームになる
yeah exactly
うん正確
okay a new malware called Judy is now
大丈夫、 Judyと 呼ばれる新しいマルウェア が今
infecting millions of Android
数百万のAndroidを感染させる
smartphones globally close on the heels
スマートフォンは世界的にハイヒールで閉じる
of the wanna cry holding pcs at ransom
身代金で PC を抱いて泣きたい
according to security solutions firm
セキュリティソリューション会社によると
checkpoint the malware Judy uses
Judyが使用するマルウェアをチェックポイントする
infected devices to generate large
感染したデバイスは 大きな
amounts of fraudulent clicks on
不正な クリック数
advertisements generating revenues for
広告収入
the perpetrators behind it the total
その後ろの加害者たち
spread of the malware campaign on Google
マルウェアキャンペーンのGoogleへの普及
Play Google's official app store may
Googleの公式アプリストアを再生することがあります
have reached between eight point five
8つのポイントの間に達した
and thirty six point five million users
36人の500万人のユーザー
checkpoints said in its blog the auto
チェックポイントはブログで auto
clicking adware duty was found on forty
アドウェアの義務をクリックしたのは40
one apps developed by a Korean company
韓国企業が開発した1つのアプリ
however it wasn't clear which countries
しかし、 どの国
have been impacted by the Judy malware
ジュディマルウェア の 影響を受けています
some of that some of the apps that were
いくつかのアプリの中には
infected we discovered resided on Google
私たちがGoogleに居住していることを発見した
Play for several years but all were
何年もプレイしていたが、すべてが
recently updated it's unclear how long
最近更新された
the malicious code existed inside the
悪質なコードが
apps hence the actual spread of the
アプリの実際の普及率
malware remains unknown it added after a
マルウェアは依然として不明で、それは 後に追加しました
checkpoint notified Google about this
チェックポイントはこれについて Googleに通知しました
threat the apps were swiftly removed
脅威のアプリは迅速に削除されました
from the Play Store
Playストアから
said the blog well that's good Intel has
インテルが持っている良いブログだと言った
unveiled a new x-series platform up to
新しいxシリーズプラットフォームを発表
18 cores and 36 threads AMD announced
18コアと36スレッドAMD発表
its new high-end desktop platform h EDT
新しいハイエンドデスクトッププラットフォーム h EDT
their 16 core 3232 threads thread Ripper
彼らの16コア3232スレッドのスレッド リッパー
a couple of weeks ago now at Computex in
数週間前、今のComputex で の
Taipei its Intel's turn to update its
台北の Intelは、
HEV T platform and it is one-nothing AMD
HEV Tのプラットフォームとそれは 何もない AMD
in the process the Intel platform
このプロセスでは、Intelプラットフォーム
consisting of the new x2 9 9 chipset and
新しいx2 9 9チップセットと
new x-series processors will go all the
新しいxシリーズプロセッサはすべて の
way up to 18 cores and 36 threads the h
18個のコアと36件のスレッド Hまでの道
EDT segment is aimed at gamers video
EDT セグメントは、ゲーマー向けのビデオです
streamers and content creators with deep
ストリーマー、コンテンツ制作者
pockets or an insatiable desire more
ポケットや飽くなき欲求 以上
concurrent with more concurrent starts
より多くの同時起動と並行
the mainstream processor segment has to
メインストリームプロセッサセグメントは
offer the value proposition for the
以下のための価値を提供します
segments is always a little skewed with
セグメントは常に少し 歪んでいる
the chips being as much prestige as much
チップはあまりにも多くの威信として
prestige parts as anything else
他の何かとして威信の部分
straightforward gaming workloads may May
簡単な ゲームワークロードが 5月に
struggle to make full use of the tips
ヒントをフルに活用するための奮闘
resources but serious switch streamers
重大なスイッチストリーマ
for example can make good use of the
例えば、
extra cores software developers are
余分なコアソフトウェア開発者は
another group that can make good use of
他のグループも十分に 活用 できる
all those cores the sky like X the sky
すべてのそれらの核は空のようにX空
like X Kip's
X キップのような
will also expand Intel's numbering
インテルのナンバリングも拡大するだろう
system Intel is adding a new I 9
システムIntelは新しい I 9を 追加しています
branding that slots in above the i7
i7の上にあるスロット
branding for the high end processors
ハイエンド・プロセッサ のためのブランディング
don't worry there will be some entry
いくつかの エントリ があることを心配しないでください
level X tips as well starting with
同様 で 始まる レベルXのヒント
Intel's
インテル
eye 5 line of processors the 7 640 X
目 のプロセッサー5行7 640 X
boasts 4 cores and is under 250 dollars
4つのコアを誇り、250ドル未満です
the 8 core 16 thread Intel chip costs
8コア16スレッドIntelチップコスト
599 dollars whereas AMD's corresponding
599ドルであるのに対し、 AMDの対応する
part is 499 dollars the Intel chip does
インテルの チップは499ドルです
have twice as many memory channels so
その 2倍のメモリチャネルを持っています
it's not exactly like for like but we'd
それはまさに同じ ようなものではありませんが、私たちは
expect that you'd be paying at least a
あなたは、少なくとも支払うことだろうと期待してい
little more for an Intel processor and
インテルのプロセッサ と
an until motherboard then a roughly
マザーボードまで、 おおよそ
similar AMD system thanks for watching
同様のAMD システムは 見て くれてありがとう
the category-five TV newsroom don't
カテゴリ5のTVニュースルームは
forget to Like and subscribe for all
好きには忘れて、すべてを購読する
your tech news with a slight linux bias
わずかな Linuxの偏見 であなたのハイテクニュース
and for more free content be sure to
そしてより多くの無料コンテンツのため に 確認してください
check out our website from the
から当社のウェブサイトをチェックしてください
category-five TV newsroom I'm Sasha
カテゴリ5テレビニュースルーム 私はサシャです
tomatoes
トマト
[Music]
[音楽]
[Applause]
[拍手]